Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: June 30, 2026

If you are a minor, and are not sure you understand everything in this Policy, please make sure to speak with a trusted adult before using BeReal. Please also remember that BeReal is not meant to be used if you are under 13. 

In this Privacy Policy, we will explain what information we collect about you, how we use it, when we share it, and the controls we provide you to manage the information you share with us.

1\. Information we process about you
------------------------------------

BeReal (the “App”) collects information that you provide directly to us, through your use of our App and your visit to our website or shared by third parties.

### 1.1. Data that you provide to us

The table below details the categories of personal data that you directly and voluntarily provide to us when you create an account, use the App, or interact with us.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Data Category** | **Description & Context of Collection** |
| **Account Creation Data** | When you create an account on our App, we will ask you for the following information: your phone number, full name, email address, date of birth and username. During (or after) account creation there is also some additional information you can decide to share with us: a biography, your location (as precise as you want), and a profile picture. |
| **Content Data** | When you use the App, you can decide to share the following data:<br><br>*   Photos and videos that you take (“Content”) using the App or photos that you share from your library. You can create an account without allowing us to access and collect data from your device’s camera or photo library. However, you will only be able to see your friends’ Content when you have posted your own BeReal. It’s a foundational part of how BeReal works.<br>    <br>*   Your GPS location: you can decide to share your GPS location when you share Content through our App. If you choose to share your location and you are not a minor, by default, your precise location (street level) is shared but you can switch it to your approximate location (city level). If you are a minor, your approximate location is shared by default and only if you choose to share it.<br>    <br>*   Your reaction to your friends’ Content: RealMojis, emojis, captions and comments. |
| **Chat Data** | When you use the BeReals chat function, we collect the messages, photos and videos you share with your friends within the chat. |
| **Transaction Data** | When you make an in-app purchase, your payment is processed directly by the relevant app store (Apple App Store or Google Play Store). We do not collect or store your credit card details or billing address. <br><br>  <br>  <br><br>However, to fulfill your order, grant you access to the purchased features, and maintain our financial records, we receive and process the following data: <br><br>*   Transaction IDs and digital receipt tokens. <br>    <br>*   Purchase history. <br>    <br>*   The specific virtual goods you purchased and the date of purchase. |
| **Communications with BeReal** | When you report a concern with our App, respond to a survey, request assistance, we collect the following data:<br><br>*   Your email address,<br>    <br>*   Content of communication with us,<br>    <br>*   Photos you may decide to share with us,<br>    <br>*   Copies of government-issued identification (only when strictly required to identify you with certainty),<br>    <br>*   Identifiers (e.g., phone numbers or email address),<br>    <br>*   Any other information you may decide to share with us. |

### 1.2. Data we collect when you use our App or visit our website

Like all internet based services, as you use our App or visit our website, we automatically receive information about you from your device and your usage of our App and your visit of our website. Most information is collected through trackers.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Data Category** | **Description & Context of Collection** |
| **Connection and Technical Data** | Through the use of our website: IP address, device type, operating system version, browser, language preference, and browsing data<br><br>  <br>  <br><br>Through your use of our App: <br><br>*   IP address, account creation date, last login, terminal equipment and port, operating system, system configuration data, device type, operating system version, browser, language preference, and applications.<br>    <br>*   user\_id (unique identifier generated at account creation), device\_id (unique identifier generated when connecting on new device) and Amplitude ID. |
| **Mobile advertising IDs and device identifiers** | We collect technical identifiers developed by mobile operating systems for advertising purposes which remain under your control and can be reset or erased at any time through your device settings:<br><br>*   Mobile advertising IDs (e.g., Apple IDFA if you use iOS or Google AAID if you use Android).<br>    <br>*   Device identifiers (e.g., IDFV for iOS devices and Android ID for Android devices). |
| **Interaction Data** | Friend (number of friends, friend invitations, the friends with whom you interact the most). |
| **Inferred Information** | We will analyse Account Creation Data and the Content Data to infer information about you:<br><br>*   Your time zone.<br>    <br>*   Your likely interests derived from the visual elements of your photos, used exclusively as internal targeting criteria.<br>    <br>*   Your likely gender, inferred via AI from your username, first name and biography, used exclusively as internal targeting criteria. |
| **Usage Data** | Actions performed on the App or our website, time of posting Content, how many times you retook a photo before posting, number of BeReal posts, Content viewed, Content interactions, the fact that you deleted Content, or that you blocked users, when you take a screenshot in our App, App crashes, pages visited and event logs. |
| **Geolocation Data** | When you use our App, we infer your country, city, region based on your IP address. |
| **Address Book Data** | You can decide to allow BeReal to access your address book to identify the friends in your Address Book who may already be on BeReal or to recommend you new friends. We do not access your Address Book without your permission. Bear in mind that even if you don’t agree to share your Address Book with us, we can still make personalized friends’ suggestions to you based on your contact details that we received from your friends who use our App (see below). You can revoke your permission to access your Address Book Data at any time through your device settings. Once access is revoked, we will no longer collect or update contact information from your address book, and previously uploaded contact data will be deleted within a reasonable time. |
| **UX Interaction Recordings** | For a randomized sample of users (0.001%), we record technical interactions with the App interface, such as touching and swiping. This is conducted through our analytic partner to help us visualize how users navigate the App and improve the overall user interface. This processing is not deployed in all geographic regions and may not apply depending on your location. This data is kept for a maximum of 90 days from the time of collection and is then automatically deleted. |

### 1.3. Information about you provided by third parties

The table below details the categories of personal data that we receive about you from third parties, and the context in which we receive them.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Source** | **Description & Context of Collection** |
| **Other users of the App** | We may receive information about you from other users of our App. For instance, if other users know you and choose to use contact importing, they may share your contact details, such as your phone number, with us, just as you may share theirs. Where friends of yours use contact importing, we may suggest you as a friend to them, and them as a friend to you, or they can find you via our search tool. |
| **Integrations with Partners** | When you decide to connect a partner application (for example Spotify) to use a specific integration on BeReal, we receive information that allows us to bring that feature to you. This will include all necessary device data, and other optional data that you may choose to share as part of the integration. |
| **Our partners** | We receive information about where you came from to download the App (for example, if you clicked on an ad on another social media). |
| **Advertisers** | When an advertiser runs a campaign with us, it may provide us with a hashed (pseudonymized) list of phone numbers of its own customers. We match this list against hashed phone numbers associated with BeReal user accounts in order to display that advertiser’s ads to the relevant users on BeReal. We do not receive phone numbers in clear text from advertisers, and hashed values provided for matching are not kept beyond the matching operation. |

2\. How we use information we receive about you
-----------------------------------------------

The table below outlines the purposes for which we process your personal data, the specific categories of data involved, and the legal bases we rely on for each processing activity.

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Purpose of Processing** | **Categories of Personal Data** | **Legal Basis** |
| Creating and maintaining your account, and identifying you when you log in | Account Creation Data | Performance of our contract with you |
| Enabling you to publish, see and react to Content on the BeReal App and use BeReal’s chat | Content Data, Chat Data, Communications with BeReal, Usage Data, Connection and Technical Data | Performance of our contract with you |
| Processing and managing your in-app purchases, providing access to paid features or subscriptions, and handling related billing inquiries | Account Creation Data, Transaction Data, Communications with BeReal, Connection and Technical Data | Performance of our contract with you, and compliance with our legal obligations (e.g., accounting and consumer protection laws for retaining transaction records) |
| Determining your time zone and informing you of the time to post your Content | Connection and Technical Data | Our legitimate interest in providing you with our App (you can change your time zone at any time in the settings of the App) |
| Processing your or other users’ requests, complaints and reports | Content Data, Communications with BeReal | Our legitimate interest in responding to requests regarding our App or the Content displayed |
| Moderating Content in accordance with the law (prevention of illegal activities, fraud, cyber harassment, etc.) and our Terms | Content Data, Usage Data, Chat Data | Compliance with our legal obligations (BeReal is required by law to retain this information in certain cases) |
| Suspending accounts or preventing certain users from using the App after a violation of applicable law or our Terms | Account Creation Data, Interaction Data | Our legitimate interest in providing a safe and secure environment in accordance with our Terms |
| Connecting you with your friends by providing you with personalized friend suggestions, showing you which contacts to invite to the App and recommending new friends | Address Book Data, Interaction Data | Your consent to access your Address Book Data, and our legitimate interest in using the data received |
| Communicating with you within the App, for example about a feature of our App | Account Creation Data, Content Data | Your consent (managed through your device settings, as for notifications) |
| Sending you account-related text messages (SMS) such as security alerts, interruptions or maintenance, and information about account deletion | Account Creation Data | Performance of our contract with you |
| Sending you promotional text messages (SMS) such as special events or offers from BeReal | Account Creation Data | Your consent, where required by applicable law; otherwise, our legitimate interest |
| Ensuring the App or the website runs smoothly for you | Connection and Technical Data, Usage Data | Our legitimate interest in providing a working App and website |
| Identifying you to your account when you have lost access | Communications with BeReal | Our legitimate interest in restoring your access to your account |
| Inferring your likely interests from your pictures and gender from your username, first name and biography, used as criteria to select relevant ads for you on the App | Content Data, Account Creation Data | Your consent, where required by applicable law; otherwise, our legitimate interest |
| Serving advertising tailored to your preferences and interests, whether the ads are selected by our ad network partners or us (i.e.: selecting the most relevant advertising for you, including by matching hashed audience lists provided by advertisers against your account, displaying advertising on our App, and measuring advertising performance) | Connection and Technical Data, Inferred Information, phone number from Account Creation Data (hashed for this purpose), hashed phone-number lists provided by advertisers, Mobile advertising IDs and device identifiers | Your consent, where required by applicable law; otherwise, our legitimate interest |
| Measuring our App’s and website’s effectiveness, the performance of the App (e.g., crashes and causes of crashes) or our website, and its stability | Usage Data, Connection and Technical Data | Our legitimate interest in providing a functional App and website that meets your expectations |
| Choosing and publishing Content on BeReal’s discovery feed | Content Data, Interaction Data | Our legitimate interest in providing a public feed (you can choose, each time you post, whether your post is visible on the public feed) |
| Carrying out surveys and gathering your feedback for research or product testing purposes | Communications with BeReal | Our legitimate interest in improving our App (you can choose, each time, whether to participate in a survey) |
| Ensuring your and other users’ safety and security, the security of our App or website and our partners, and compliance with relevant laws and regulations | Content Data, Chat Data, Communications with BeReal, Usage Data, Connection and Technical Data | Our legitimate interest in providing a safe and secure environment in accordance with our Terms |
| Responding to requests from national authorities | Account Creation Data, Content Data, Connection and Technical Data, Interaction Data, Mobile advertising IDs and device identifiers, Geolocation Data | Compliance with our legal obligations, or where there is no direct legal obligation, our legitimate interest in cooperating with national authorities |
| Defending and asserting our rights before the authorities (civil, criminal or administrative) | All categories of data | Our legitimate interest in asserting and defending our rights |
| Improving your experience (UX) by analyzing how you interact with our features and interface | UX Interaction Recordings, Usage Data, Connection and Technical Data | Your consent, where required by applicable law; otherwise, our legitimate interest |

3\. When we share information about you
---------------------------------------

We share information about you with our employees and service providers, who will process it under our control:

*   **BeReal Employees**: To allow you to use the App or to provide you support, authorized BeReal employees may need to get access to your information. We strictly limit who can access your data.
    
*   **Service Providers**: To bring you our App we work with a small group of partners who provide us services. This includes partners who help with technical and hosting support, sending notifications, publishing, and sharing content, [user analytics](https://amplitude.com/privacy) and satisfaction surveys, management of security incidents or fraudulent activity, etc. In working with those partners, we may share your information with them to bring you our App.
    
*   **Counsels**: For compliance with our statutory obligations, in particular in terms of accounting, auditing and internal control, we might share your information with our counsels (legal, financial, audit).

We also share information about you to third parties, who will process it under their own control:

*   **Ad Partners**: To allow us to monetize the ad inventory of our App and provide users with free products and services, we work with advertising networks and mediation partners. These partners may collect information directly from your device or your use of the App through their own tools, such as software development kits (“SDKs”) or cookies, in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will find a list of our partners and their privacy policies that describe their practices and allow you to exercise your rights directly toward them [here](https://help.bereal.com/hc/en-us/articles/19494197955101-Ad-Partners). 
    
*   **Commercial partners**: From time to time, we may share some Content data to promote our services to our commercial partners.
    
*   **Partner Integrations**: Where we partner to bring you a feature we may need to share your information with the partner to integrate the feature into our App.
    
*   **Legal and Statutory Purposes**: From time to time we may receive legal requests for information related to our users, be required to proactively share data with authorities (governmental authorities, courts, and similar third parties) when we learn of certain Content on our App (e.g., Child Sexual Abuse Material or terrorism), address fraud or security concerns, or protect people on our App or elsewhere from harm.
    
*   **Change in Ownership**: In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or bankruptcy, BeReal may share, sell or transfer information about you. This Privacy Policy would apply to all transferred information.

4\. Children’s data
-------------------

BeReal never knowingly or willingly collects any personal data concerning children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13, please do not use BeReal.

5\. International transfers
---------------------------

Some of the partners and service providers referred to in this policy are located outside of the European Union.

In such case, we ensure that:

*   The personal data is transferred to countries recognized as offering an equivalent level of protection or,
    
*   One of the mechanisms offering appropriate guarantees is implemented (for example, the adoption of the standard contractual clauses of the European Commission).

6\. How long we keep information about you
------------------------------------------

We keep your information only for as long as it’s needed to provide our services to you, in line with legal requirements and data protection authorities guidelines.

To minimize data retention, your account and associated data will be permanently deleted in the event of prolonged inactivity. For the purposes of this policy, the period of inactivity is calculated from the date of your last activity, which is strictly defined as your most recent login or connection to the App. Specifically, to minimize data retention, your account may be deleted after three (3) years of continuous inactivity if you are located in the United States, or after two (2) years of continuous inactivity if you are located in Europe or any other jurisdiction outside of the United States. BeReal may send you a prior notice via text message (SMS) to the phone number associated with your account before the scheduled deletion, giving you the opportunity to log in and keep your account active.

Certain information may be archived for a longer period if BeReal received a valid legal request requiring us to preserve your information or to prevent permanently suspended users from creating new accounts. Additionally, we are legally required to retain Transaction Data and related financial records for a longer period (up to ten years) to comply with tax, accounting, and consumer protection laws. 

7\. What controls you have over your information in the App
-----------------------------------------------------------

At BeReal we have implemented features to ensure that you remain in control of your personal data.

**Notification**: You grant permission to receive notifications at the level of your device settings, and you can withdraw it there at any time. In the settings of the App, you can also choose and control which notifications you receive about our App.

**Block or Hide Users**: To make sure you have a great experience when using our App, you can block or hide users who you do not want to receive Content from or who you do not want to see your Content. If you block or hide a user, at any time you can go into the settings of the App and view who you have blocked or hidden. You can also unblock or unhide them at any time.

**Who sees your Content**: Note that when you share Content through our App, that Content is available to your BeReal friends. Each time you share Content, you can also decide to allow friends of your friends to see it or even to publish it on BeReal’s discovery feed. You can control this at any time in the settings of the App. How other users use your Content is not under our control.

**Time Zone**: When you create an account we determine your time zone for the purpose of providing you our App. In the settings of the App you can change your time zone at any time.

**Integrations**: From time to time we may offer integrations with partners to provide you certain features. If those partners require you to log into your account on their services to avail of the feature, you will be able to control those integrations in the settings of the App at any time.

**Deactivate Memories**: In the settings of the App, you can choose to activate or deactivate the memories feature at any time. If you deactivate this feature, you and other users of the App won’t be able to see your prior Content.

**Delete Your Account**: In the settings of the App, you can choose to delete your account at any time. If you choose to delete your account, your account will be scheduled for deletion. This process takes approximately 15 days. If you log back into your account during that 15 day period, it will stop the deletion request. If you do not log back in, your account and all of your information will be permanently deleted. Note, information will not be deleted where BeReal has received a valid legal request requiring us to preserve your information.

**Consent :** When we rely on your consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time from the App settings. Specifically, to exercise your choices regarding the sharing of your data with Ad Partners and the use of machine learning to analyze your photos and profile information for internal ad targeting, you can go to the "Privacy" settings within the App and select "Modify my consents".

**SMS Communications**: You can choose to stop receiving promotional text messages (SMS) from us at any time. To opt-out, you can simply reply "STOP" to any promotional message you receive or update your communication preferences directly in the settings of the App. Please note that even if you opt-out of promotional messages, we may still send you non-promotional, account-related text messages, such as security alerts, interruptions or maintenance, information about account deletion, etc.

8\. What rights do you have over your information
-------------------------------------------------

Privacy is a fundamental human right. That means every person that uses our App, irrespective of where they reside, can expect the same things from us. Whether you are in Europe, one of the 50 U.S. States, Latin America, the Middle East, Africa, Japan, Asia Pacific, or anywhere in between, you can:

*   **Right to access and obtain a copy of your data**: you may request access to your personal data. If you request such access, we will provide you with all the information required by law, including the purposes of the processing, the categories of data processed, the categories of recipients, the data retention periods and your rights.
    
*   **Right of rectification**: You may also ask us to rectify any personal data concerning you that is inaccurate and to complete any incomplete information.
    
*   **Right to erasure/deletion**: Under certain circumstances, you may request the erasure of your personal data. We may nevertheless need to retain certain limited data in an archived database, in particular if we have a legal obligation to retain such personal data or if it is necessary for the exercise or defense of legal claims.
    
*   **Right to restrict processing**: In certain circumstances, you may request the limitation of the processing of your personal data, in particular when you request the rectification of your personal data.
    
*   **Right to withdraw your consent**: Where the processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you may, at any time, withdraw any consent you have previously provided to us. Such withdrawal does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent prior to withdrawal.
    
*   **Right to object**: You may also object at any time to the processing of your Personal Data when it is used for commercial prospecting purposes or for reasons related to your particular situation.
    
*   **Right to portability**: In certain cases, you may also obtain a copy of your personal data, in a commonly used and machine-readable format, to enable you to exercise your right to data portability.
    
*   **Right to set instructions for how your data is processed post-mortem**: If you are a French user, you also have the right to set directives concerning the management of your personal data after your death.

If you are in the European Union, EFTA States or the United Kingdom, and wish to raise a concern about our data processing practices, you have the right to do so with your local supervisory authority or BeReal’s lead supervisory authority, the Commission Nationale de l’Informatique et des Libertés (CNIL), using the [contact details listed on their website](https://www.cnil.fr/en/contact-us).

Some of these rights (rectification, deletion and consent withdrawal) can be exercised directly from the App, in the setting section. You can also exercise these rights and all other rights by addressing your request to our Data Protection Team  at [dpo@bere.al](mailto:dpo@bere.al). Since we don’t necessarily collect your email address, we sometimes will need additional information to make sure that the request does come from you.

9\. U.S. Privacy Rights
-----------------------

This section supplements our Privacy Policy and applies to residents of U.S. states whose consumer privacy laws apply to BeReal. Depending on your state of residence, some rights may not apply, or may apply differently.

This section is intended to address U.S. state consumer privacy laws that apply to BeReal, including the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended, and similar U.S. state consumer privacy laws, in each case where they apply to BeReal.

### 9.1. Personal Information We Collect

The categories of personal information we collect are described in Section 1, "Information we process about you". In the last twelve (12) months, we may have collected the following categories of personal information:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Category of personal information** | **Examples** |
| Identifiers | Name, username, phone number, email address if you contact us, IP address, user ID, device ID, mobile advertising IDs and other device identifiers. |
| Customer records information | Account details, support communications, address book contacts if you choose to share them, and other information you provide to us. |
| Commercial information | Transaction IDs, receipt tokens, purchase history, purchased virtual goods or paid features, and purchase dates. |
| Internet or other electronic network activity information | App and website usage, event logs, content viewed, content interactions, screenshots taken in the App, retakes, crashes, pages visited and similar technical activity. |
| Geolocation information | Approximate location inferred from your IP address and, if you choose to share it, GPS location attached to Content. |
| Audio, electronic, visual or similar information | Photos, videos, profile pictures, RealMojis, captions, comments, chat messages and other Content you choose to create or share. |
| Inferences | Time zone, interests or preferences inferred from your activity, Content or other signals, including interests inferred from visual elements of photos and likely gender inferred from your profile information (username, name, biography) for internal ad selection. |
| Sensitive personal information, where applicable | Precise GPS location if you choose to share it, government-issued identification if strictly required to verify your identity, contents of private communications where treated as sensitive by applicable law, and any other information treated as sensitive under applicable law. |

We do not seek to infer sensitive characteristics from your photos, videos or other Content for advertising purposes.

### 9.2. Sources of Personal Information

We collect personal information from:

*   You, when you create an account, use BeReal, post Content, use chat, make choices in the App, contact us or participate in surveys;
    
*   Your device and your use of the App or website;
    
*   Other users, for example when they upload address book contacts or interact with your Content;
    
*   App stores and payment providers, for in-app purchase records;
    
*   Partners and service providers, for example analytics, attribution, advertising, security, hosting, support and technical service providers.
    
*   Advertisers, when they provide hashed lists of their own customers’ phone numbers for advertising matching campaigns on BeReal.

### 9.3. How We Use Personal Information

We use personal information for the purposes described in Section 2, "How we use information we receive about you". These purposes include providing and securing BeReal, creating and maintaining accounts, enabling Content sharing and chat, processing purchases, providing support, moderating Content, preventing fraud and abuse, complying with legal obligations, improving the App and website, measuring performance, conducting analytics, and, where permitted and subject to your choices, providing or measuring advertising.

### 9.4. Disclosure of Personal Information

We disclose personal information to the categories of recipients described in Section 3, "When we share information about you". In the last twelve (12) months, we may have disclosed the categories of personal information listed in Section 9.1 to the following categories of recipients:

*   Service providers and processors, such as hosting providers, cloud infrastructure providers, analytics providers, security providers, communication providers, customer support providers and payment-related service providers;
    
*   Professional advisers, such as legal, accounting, audit and compliance advisers;
    
*   Advertising and measurement partners, subject to your choices and applicable law;
    
*   Integration partners, when you choose to connect a partner service to BeReal;
    
*   Public authorities, courts, law enforcement or other third parties where required or permitted by law;
    
*   Another entity in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, asset sale or similar transaction.

### 9.5. Sale, Sharing and Targeted Advertising

We do not sell personal information as traditionally understood. However, under some U.S. state privacy laws, certain advertising or measurement activities may be considered a "sale", "sharing" or processing for "targeted advertising".

In the last twelve (12) months, we may have sold, shared or processed for targeted advertising the following categories of personal information: identifiers, device identifiers, mobile advertising IDs, internet or other electronic network activity information, approximate geolocation information, and advertising-related inferences. We use interest categories and inferred gender for internal ad selection, but we do not sell or share those specific categories with advertisers. We do not sell or share your private chat messages, government-issued identification or precise GPS location with advertisers.

For advertiser audience matching based on phone numbers, advertisers provide us with hashed phone-number lists, and we do not disclose BeReal users’ phone numbers or matched audience lists back to advertisers.

You can opt out of sale, sharing and targeted advertising by going to the "Privacy" settings within the App and selecting "Modify my consents", or by contacting us at [dpo@bere.al](mailto:dpo@bere.al).

### 9.6. Sensitive Personal Information

We use sensitive personal information only as reasonably necessary to provide and secure BeReal, comply with law, prevent fraud or abuse, verify identity where needed, provide features you choose to use, or for other purposes permitted by applicable law.

If we use or disclose sensitive personal information for purposes that give you a right to limit under applicable law, we will provide a way for you to exercise that right.

### 9.7. Your U.S. Privacy Rights

Depending on your state of residence, you may have some or all of the following rights:

*   **Right to know or access**: you may request information about the personal information we collect, use, disclose, sell, share or otherwise process about you.
    
*   **Right to receive a copy**: you may request a copy of certain personal information we maintain about you in a portable and, where technically feasible, readily usable format.
    
*   **Right to delete**: you may request that we delete personal information we collected from or about you, subject to legal exceptions.
    
*   **Right to correct**: you may request that we correct inaccurate personal information we maintain about you.
    
*   **Right to opt out of sale, sharing or targeted advertising**: you may opt out of certain advertising-related disclosures or processing.
    
*   **Right to opt out of certain profiling**: where applicable, you may opt out of profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. BeReal does not currently engage in this type of profiling.
    
*   **Right to limit the use and disclosure of sensitive personal information**: where this right applies, you may ask us to limit certain uses or disclosures of sensitive personal information.
    
*   **Right to appeal**: where required by law, you may appeal our decision if we deny your privacy request.
    
*   **Right to non-discrimination**: we will not discriminate against you for exercising your privacy rights.

### 9.8. How to Exercise Your Rights

You can exercise certain choices directly in the App, including deletion of your account and withdrawal or modification of consent where available. You may also submit a request by contacting our Data Protection Team at [dpo@bere.al](mailto:dpo@bere.al).

To protect your account and other users, we may need to verify your identity before fulfilling certain requests. We may ask you to provide information that matches information we already maintain about you. If you make a request through an authorized agent, we may require proof that the agent is authorized to act on your behalf, and we may ask you to verify your identity directly with us, unless applicable law provides otherwise.

We will respond to access, deletion, correction and portability requests within 45 days, unless a shorter period is required by applicable law. If permitted by law, we may extend this period once and will explain the reason for the extension. We will honor opt-out requests for sale, sharing and targeted advertising as soon as reasonably possible and within the time required by applicable law. For California residents, we will process opt-out requests no later than 15 business days after receipt.

If your state gives you a right to appeal and you wish to appeal our decision on your request, you can contact us at [dpo@bere.al](mailto:dpo@bere.al) and include "Privacy Appeal" in the subject line.

10\. Contact
------------

The data controller for our App is BeReal SAS, with a registered office located at 59 Rue Jean-Jacques Rousseau 75001 - Paris (France), and which is registered under number 881 079 685 with the Paris Trade and Companies Registry.

If you have a question about our Privacy Policy, you can reach our Data Protection Team at [dpo@bere.al](mailto:dpo@bere.al).

11\. Update of our Privacy Policy
---------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time if this is necessary or if the law requires it.
